https://www.orsa.ca/privacy/

Map | Photos
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Ottawa Regional Society of Architects collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.orsa.ca website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Ottawa Regional Society of Architects.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Ottawa Regional Society of Architects may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
– To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
– To process payments
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
– To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Ottawa Regional Society of Architects has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Ottawa Regional Society of Architects
www.orsa.ca
P.O. Box 56117 Ottawa, Ontario K1R 7Z1
secretary@orsa.ca
This document was last updated on January 31, 2014.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Featured Member
Douglas VandenHam
Featured Supporter
Tweet
ORSA
What we do
Mandate / Mission
Board Members
Supporters
Contacts
Find an architect
Search Member Firms by name:
Select a firm
A4 Architecture + designChristopher Simmonds ArchitectGRC ArchitectsHobin Architecture
Search Member Firms by specialty:
Select a specialization
3D Modeling & VisualizationBuilding ScienceCommercial - retail, offices, restaurantsDesign Build ServicesEducational FacilitiesGeneral PracticeHealthcare FacilitiesHeritage ConservationHigh-tech FacilitiesHospitality & LeisureIndustrialInstitutionalInteriorsOtherResidential - multi-unitResidential - single-familySpecifications WritingSustainabilityTransportation FacilitiesUrban Design & Planning
Search ORSA Members:
Select a user
Savy NhimAMMAR AL-DUJAILIAmin AminAlice AnneAhmed ArefAndrew BouwmanAnthony Domenic BruniAndrea BuchsbaumAnastasiya BurchevskaAndrew ButlerAzad ChichmanianAmanda ConfortiAndre CousineauAnton FreundorferAmanda GilbertAnnegret HaywardAngella Hercules StevensonAlexis Maria Caja HoffmannAllan HubleyAdel IskandarAshraf KinawiAmy KlassenAlberto KleinAdrienne KrommAlain LafondAmanda LawrenceAnthony LeaningAnh Le QuangAlex LeungAl MackeyAmjed MansourAlain-Serge MarchandArt MawAlison MichelinAtena MirshahiAnthea MumbyAnita MurrayAli NajafdariAntoine CousineauAllison NielsenAnnegret HaywardAnthony Pearsonalma rahmaniAmy RancierAndrew ReevesAllison RogersAlex SargentAnnie-Claude SauveAba SimpsonAlex SmythAngelo SpadolaAnthony SproulAllan TeramuraAndrew ThomAndrew ToddAlexander VriendAlex WellerBernard BenoitBryan BonellBrynne CampbellBrian CasagrandeBrian K. ClarkBarry CraigMathieu DufourBrigitte DesrochersBrian W. DickeyBernie DuquetteBrian EamesBrian HallBrett HarrisBarry J. HobinBrigitte HubertBrandon LawrenceBenoit MarandaBob MonetteBrigitte NBobby IlgBrendan OhUiginnBarry L. PadolskyBrent ReistBrent BelangerBrent ReistBill RitceyJeff FitchBill SahidBruno St.JeanOlalekan AboderinBrock WilsonBrenda WongBrooke ZacharukChloe AllinChristopher BernotasCharles BlaisCatherine BonierClive BroomfieldChris DeimlingChristopher DziwinskiCathie EdmondCraig GillierCaitlin HandyChristopher HoytChris CormierChristopher IlgCarolyn JonesChristopher KnightClarice KramerChris LanceChristine LegaultChristopher LeggettCamille LewisColin MajidCatherine McKenneyChristopher MoiseClaudia NatesClaude ProvencherClaudio Brun del ReC.P. SharmaChristopher SimmondsChristopher ThuemenClaude TremblayChristopher TudinCristina Ureche-TrifuChristopher WanczyckiChristopher WardenDarrell deGrandmontDAVID AVELLADavid BeckerDenis de BellefeuilleDaniel BoulangerDouglas BrooksDarren BrunneDavid J. BrydenDavid BullDouglas Joseph CardinalDarcy CharltonDavid ChernushenkoDouglas ClanceyDavid ColeDomenic CostantinoDavid M. CoutoDanielle CoutureDiane DeansDanny DingDan DufortDeanne DuncanDavid DunnDerek CrainDarrell FisherDrew GareauDenis GingrasDouglas HardieDoug HarrisonDaniel J. HenhoefferDarryl HoodDavid A. JefferiesDanica LauDonald MacDonaldDamian MacLellanDenise MartelDavid McConnachieDavid McRobieDenise LepageDavid MungallDave OlivieriDiane E PhillipsDouglas PinnellDouglas PollardDanica RobertsonDerek RuddyDinko SakanovicDino Di SanoDavid StoneDominique TheriaultDouglas VandenHamDaniela VeismanDiane Elizabeth WhalenDaniel WojcikDanielle WojtyniakDeborah YatesElie BourgetEvelyne CardinalElizabeth CaronEdward CuhaciErin DuncanEli El-ChantiryEric GirardEric HaarEdward HopeEric HuotEric LaflammeEric LeitnerEd LindeEmily Webster MasonErica MayerErick McEvoyElana McIntoshEva OnufrakErnie PattonEarl ReinkeEva RussellEmmanuelle Van RuttenElliot ShermanEliseo TempranoE. Jane WilsonElaine YeeElizabeth ZdanskyFrederico ArcieroMiranda PaquetteFareed DeanFarhan HaqqaniFrank HeartyFrancis PelletierFrance PellicanoFrank PuentesFred SchrieverGeorge BemiGeoffrey BennellGuillermo L. CeppiGerry ConwayGeorge DarouzeGerrie DoyleGord ErskineGregory FryGilla GeigerGilles J. GobeilGeoff HodginsGordon KingGlen KlymGordon KriegGord LorimerGuy MonetteGolchehr MonjazebGerald MorrisGraham MurfittGrant Oikawagabriel prostGabriel RivestGilles St-JeanGuillermo BourgetGerard VerriereHamid AghashahiHoury AvedissianHugo Beland-LatrielleHenning BruchmullerHuston EubankHugo GagnonHarish GuptaBrian HierlihyHeather McArthurHugh O'Brienhoda jafarianHonorata Pienkowska-RosemanHeather SempleHeloise ThibodeauHarold ZapataIan YoungRosemarie AlbertIsabelle BradburyIan CraigIvan DesrochesIhor HrytskivIgor KidisyukIan KubanekIsidora ParezanovicIdwal D. RichardsIsabel RicherIain StuartIan WillsonIan YoungJohn AbelJameela BhagatJanice Van BaarenJoyce BaddourJames BellJames BemiJosee BerubeJaime Betancur-ArroyaveJohn Blias-CabezasJames BrazeauJames ChapmanJean CloutierJames ColizzaJohn CookJames CurtissJean DallaireJean DaoustJayla DeKrakerJohn DeVriesJohn DonkinJeff ChaputJenny LafranceJordan EllisJean EmmellJesscia KirkhamJason FlynnJean FournierJ. Marsh FrereJim GeddesJoseph GembilloJason GillmorJeff GoettlingJon GravellJade Labonte-GregoryJ. Anthony GriffithsJean-Daniel GrobJayant GuptaJoshua HaleJanis HamacherJan HarderJonathan HarperJames HayesJennifer HeaneyJohn-David HutchisonJan KapsaJohn KealeyJustin LafontaineJustin LangoisJeff LeiperJean-Marie L'HeureuxJay LimJohn LiptakJeff LivingstonJames MaddiganJenna MawJean PellandJoey PelosoJosee Anne PronovostJennifer RedmanJulie RoyJohn SalimJoseph Denis SeguinJessie SmithJeffrey SnyderJill SparlingJane ThompsonJean-Francois TrahanJenny TrinhJulia GersovitzJulie CharronJuwana Abu-ZeinahJan VeerJim WatsonJeff WoodwardJim YamashitaJozef ZorkoKarine BoivinKristopher BenesKent BugatschKathleen O'Neill ColeKate CoulthartKeith DickieKeith EgliKsenia EicKeith EvansKarl FischerKatarzyna GoneraKaren GriffithKaj J.E. GrolleKeith JohnsonKimberly KennedyKelly KorolukKatelyn LucasKen MerkleyKristine NadonKyle ScharfKaren StidwillKelly KorolukYelena AbrosimovLaura ClarkLynne BalaberdaLuke BoonstraLaurie BouchardLinda ChapmanLaura Lynn Da SilvaLouis CormierLouise CowleyLoretta DabayLeila EmmrysLinda FogazziLauren GruszeckiLucien HaddadLauren HallLe Leslie HuynhLouise LalandeLouis-T LemayLouise McGuganLara McKendrickLiza MedekLeon MercierLydia MillerLuc NugentLeslie PapineauLinda RheaultLuminita SerbanescuLeon SlabbertLee Ann SneddenLynne StricklandLaura UrrechagaLen WardLesley D. WatsonMartin LeblancMohammed al RiffaiMaryam MirsepassiManon Barel-LeungMegan BeangeM. David BlakelyMyriam BoucherMark Thompson BrandtMary Anne BullMark CardealMaria CarrierMei ChowMark D'AgostinoMichele DredgeMelissa Du PlessisMarianne DupontMarwa El-KadyMarwa El-KadyMarie-Éve SimardMaguy EustacheMathieu FleuryMasaharu FukushimaMurray GallantMatthew GallowayMarc GauthierMarjan GhannadMark GlassfordMelanie GodinMark GordonMichel GravelMijanou GravelleMatthew HenningMichael HodginsMark HollettMatthew IppersielMichele DredgeMatthew JohnstonMuhammad KareemMara KlammrodtMichael KorolMelanie LamontagneMona N. LamontagneMarcel LandryMarc LangloisMathieu LapalmeMichael LapradeMario LeBlancMelissa LengiesMichelle LensonMarc MainvilleMarco ManconiMaurizio S. MartignagoMichelle MaybeeMaggie McCannMarta McDermottMadeleine MeilleurMorris MelamedMagalie MichelMegan MolsonRosa Margarita Montes VieraMichael PeixotoMark Lawrence PesnerMartine PfalzgrafMarie PoirierMichael PutmanMichael QaqishMelissa ReevesMelanie RicherMark RosenMarie-Andree RoyMichael StottMonique St. PierreMichael SullivanMansoor SuteirMark TaylorMarc ThiviergeMartin TiteMiguel TremblayMuktirajsinhji ChauhanMelissa WakefieldMike WatsonMalcolm WildeboerMarianne WilkinsonNupur AgrawalNancy MacEwenNicole AndersonNathalie RouthierM.Ali NavidbakhshNatalia BarretoNicholas Kimon CaragianisNupur ChakravortyNina DeGiovanniNicolas MaaloufNathalie MarionNatalie MullerNicole PeirceNatasha PlotnikovNatalie SmithNicholas L. De SocioOrhan HassanPaul McQueenPatrick BissonPeter ClarkPaul CooperPeter CroftPaul CunninghamPeter M. DarwishPeter DodsworthPaul DolanPhilippe DoylePatrick DubucEric PempusPeter CaiPawel FiettPatrick FlorentPaul HussarPaul KarioukPeter KellyPeter J. KindreePatrick LajeunessePaul LamontPaul LavalleePierre LeclercPatricia LiptakPaolo MarinelliPeter R. MoyPhilip J.F. PiazzaPeter RankinPatrick RenshawPeter SimisterPierre TabetPaul ZylstraRon AllardRamon Renderos SotoSophie JanneyRadim BohacekRobin BonelloRichard BriginshawRitchard BrisbinRiley BrockingtonRick ChiarelliRichard ChmielRegis CoteRebecca DamDaniel HemmingRob FarisRebecca FernandoRichard FouchardRobert FroomRichard GurnhamRosaline Judith HillRenee HynesRebecca JamesRichard JolyRick KellnerRichard KempRyan KoslowskiRheal LabelleRoderick LaheyRichard LimmertRobert Van LinTina BrineRick MacEwenRobert MartinRuriko NumazawaRobert MatthewsRobert MartinRyan OdellRickson M. OuthetRosalind PacigaRoger PatryRichard Glenn RamptonRajka RasevicRandall L. RomaninRandall RowatRichard SheanRichard SmithRobert smithRick TaylorRichard ThorneRalph A. Vandenbergrandolph wangRobert WebsterRichard WhiteRalph WiesbrockRobert J. WoodmanRyan Van SpronsenRan ZaigSylvain AllaireSalman Al-ShawafSampoorna BhattacharyaSam BadachShannon BassettStephen BlaisSaralyn BouwmanSheryl BoyleSteve CliffordSamuel CoxScott DareSamir DesaiSteve DesrochesSuehayla EljajiSerina FraserSuzanne GibsonScott HaywardSusan HenrySophie JanneySonia JoanisSusan JohnsStephen JonesStephan KatzSwapan Jeet KaurScott KentSteven KenyonSami KerbaScott LabrosseSteve LajeunesseSophie LamotheShawn J. LawrenceSteve LeahySarah LeeSean LundyShawn LynchSam MilneScott MoffattSue MonkSarah MurraySolange GuaidaSegun OrimoloyeShruti PooniaStephen PopeShad QadriSebastian RacineSamir RaniaStephen RobertsonSacha SauriolSilvia ScapillatiSadima ShresthaSanskriti SinghSusan SmithSophiany SomStephanie MurraySabine ToussaintChanghong SunSuzan UnittSarah WardShawn WesselSonia ZouariTarek Abdel-HameedTony BarrThomas BloodTom DubicanacTodd DuckworthTobias FellowsThao GawargyToby GreenbaumTroy HarperTodd HeadonTella Irani ShemiraniTania IrvineTessa KampmanTara LafaveTom LavertyThomas Hugh LeungThomas MasonTimothy V. MurrayTobi NussbaumBarry HobinTim RittenbergRobyn BaldwinTim StanleyTim TierneyTino TolotTitania TruesdaleVincent AlcaideValerie Lynn AllenVincent ColizzaVernesa KaramehmedovicVian MusaVeronica Nunn de PencierVladimir PopovicVeronica PorterVincent RenaudVincent SpagnoloVanessa WorrellWendy Brawley-CunliffeWilliam CromptonWilliam A. DavisAlvaro RamosWilliam B. GreggWenjun GuW. Gerard McDonaldWiliam MetzWolfgang G. MohauptWilliam PrangeWilliam A. RowlandWayne SernoskieYomna AnaniYekaterina ArtemchukYvona BohackovaYves GosselinYvonne LangenYuk-Cheung LeeYasir NaqviYoung ShawnZeynep EkimZacharie ForestZhuxi LiZoé LebelZofia JurewiczZuzana KeslerovaZoe WardZygmunt Wysocki
Membership
Fees
Register
Member Login
Events and News
Upcoming Events
Archived Events
News
